Shake your hips, girls!
Go!
Remember this.
In our industry,
service comes first.
So delicious.
I'll come again tomorrow.
What a handsome young gentleman.
Are you here alone?
Madam,
I'm looking for someone.
Madam?
Big sister,
Big sister?
Miss,
How should I
address you?
Just call me Sister.
My name is Yingxiang,
and my surname is Liu.
What a good name.
Smiling and chatting, leaving a faint fragrance behind.
I came here
for good food.
Don't be shy.
Everyone who comes here is looking for someone.
Tell me,
what kind of person are you looking for?
I don't need company today.
I heard from a friend
that the West Lake vinegar fish at Baixiang Restaurant is good.
I came here specifically
to taste it quietly.
I wonder
if you could personally taste it with me?
You want me to taste it with you?
Naturally, I need the most beautiful person by my side.
You little thing.
You're quite cute.
Yingxiang is here to welcome you.
Sister.
I think this room is pretty good.
Stop messing around.
This is the accounting room of our Baixiang Pavilion.
You can't eat here.
Sister,
this accounting room of yours
has excellent Feng Shui.
Wealth will surely roll in.
You know quite a bit about Feng Shui.
Just a little.
It's necessary for traveling the world.
I didn't expect you to be so amazing.
How about tonight,
you take me to your room
and have a good chat with me?
Sure.
Looking at your outfit, sir,
you must have returned from studying abroad.
Do you know about Western clocks?
I've seen them.
I have one of those at home.
It always rings at night,
giving me a headache
and making me anxious.
Since you're here today,
you must be a helper sent by heaven.
Why don't you
come to
my house today?
Take a good look for me.
It's all Boss Qian.
Could it be Boss Qian from Qian's Clothing Store?
How could he have any connection with Liu Yingxiang?
Twenty goats.
What do these goats and numbers represent?
To be honest with you, sister.
I came here today
to discuss a deal.
What deal?
Let's hear it.
My younger sister went missing
around here a few days ago.
I heard human traffickers are rampant lately.
I don't know where she was taken.
I'm really at my wit's end,
so I can only wander around here.
Sister,
please help me.
This...
Is that true?
Sister.
My parents died when I was young.
My sister and I
have depended on each other since childhood.
Since my sister went missing,
I've been in tears
all day, every day.
Don't you believe me, sister?
I don't know about this,
but I've heard some rumors.
Sister.
If you can help me find my sister,
let alone this money,
even if it bankrupts me
to repay you.
You will be my great benefactor.
I've been in the game of love for so many years.
I've long stopped caring
about gold and silver.
Sister.
Whatever you want,
as long as I have it
and can offer it,
I will present it with both hands
to Sister Yingxiang.
If you can
sleep with me tonight,
what's the harm in telling you some leads?
It's the best of both worlds.
Bad news, boss.
Someone seems to have entered the accounting room.
Sir.
I'll be right back.
Wait for me.
Of course.
Don't run!
Come, this way.
What did you find?
Qian's Clothing Store.
Catch him! Stop them!
Bad news, boss.
Those two have already escaped.
Escaped?
Yes.
Send someone to notify our benefactor.
And notify Boss Qian as well.
Yes.
No entry.
I'm looking for Inspector Zhou.
Why are you here again?
Reporting another case?
I was just passing by
and came to see a friend.
Is that not allowed?
Miss.
We've only met twice.
Are we friends now?
Looking at
your face,
you seem to have a conscience.
But
how can you
neglect your duties?
Hey.
Watch your mouth.
How am I neglecting my duties
and lacking a conscience?
Fine.
Then let me ask you.
Recently, many young girls have gone missing
in the concession.
Why don't you
go look for them?
This case
is still under secret investigation.
It's a classified file of our police station.
How did you know?
That's none of your business.
But if you rescue them,
I will allow you
to become a friend
of me, Huo Yining.
Become your Huo.
Interesting.
Hold my arm.
What are you doing?
We have to put on a full show.
You two.
Are you here to make clothes?
Make two qipaos for my wife.
It's an honor for our shop.
Please come with me to take your measurements, madam.
Sir,
please wait a moment.
Go ahead.
Boss.
Could you pour me a cup of tea?
No problem.
My daughter's name is Lingling.
She has been selling cigarettes at the entrance of Baixianglou Ballroom.
This Boss Qian really has a problem.
Siyao.
You're injured.
It's nothing, just a scratch.
How can you do it yourself?
I can.
You don't trust me?
Let me do it.
Senior Sister,
you're injured.
It's nothing, just a scratch.
What did you find out?
You were right.
Recently, in several main streets of the city,
young girls have gone missing.
They are mostly young female students,
or women who dress
very fashionably.
And the time of disappearance is always
at midnight or in the morning.
Disappearances have also occurred frequently in the concession.
The concession?
How do you know?
I happened to pass by,
and thought I'd trick that kid Zhou Wei.
As expected,
they are also investigating in secret.
Zhou Wei.
That means it's not a solo crime.
I heard you got injured.
Officer Ye's first day on the job.
You're doing the work of serving others.
Siyao,
I don't mean to lecture you.
You are currently suspended
and cannot investigate cases.
Why are you taking new officers to investigate cases?
You have no respect for the police station.
As a citizen,
I was injured
and brought to the police station by two officers
to bandage my wounds
and learn about the case.
Is there a problem?
What case?
We found out that Qian Yanqing, the owner of the clothing store,
is involved in the recent human trafficking
and missing girls cases,
and we have obtained relevant clues.
What are you waiting for?
Come with me to arrest him.
Alright, alright.
Apply more medicine since you're injured.
Senior Sister,
why did you tell him?
Aren't you afraid he'll ruin things?
This is called
playing hard to get.